{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 77x + 130)/(x + 8)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(x + 8) + (3x + 8)/(2x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(x + 8) * (2x + 11)/(2x + 11) + (3x + 8)/(2x + 11) * (x + 8)/(x + 8)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(2x + 11)(x + 2)/(x + 8)(2x + 11) + (x + 8)(3x + 8)/(x + 8)(2x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 49x + 51)/(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8) + (2x + 11)/(4x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5) + (2x + 11)/(4x + 5) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5)(3x + 8)/(4x + 5) + (2x + 11)/(4x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(11x^2 + 33x + 19)/(2x + 7)(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(2x + 7) + (x + 1)/(3x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(2x + 7) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) + (x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(3x + 2)(x + 2)/(2x + 7)(3x + 2) + (2x + 7)(x + 1)/(2x + 7)(3x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 51x + 64)/3(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3 + 3(x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3 * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + 3(x + 1)/(2x + 5) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)(4x + 11)/3(2x + 5) + 9(x + 1)/3(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 1)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 13x + 3)/2(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 - 2(x + 1)/(2x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) - 2(x + 1)/(2x + 1) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)(3x + 7)/2(2x + 1) - 4(x + 1)/2(2x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2(2x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 7x - 8)/2(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2 - (x + 11)/2(2x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2 * 2(2x + 1)/2(2x + 1) - (x + 11)/2(2x + 1) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)(2x + 3)/4(2x + 1) - 2(x + 11)/4(2x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(5x^2 + 13x + 9)/(x + 2)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(x + 2) + 2(x + 3)/(2x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(x + 2) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) + 2(x + 3)/(2x + 1) * (x + 2)/(x + 2)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)(2x + 3)/(x + 2)(2x + 1) + 2(x + 2)(x + 3)/(x + 2)(2x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/4(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(13x^2 + 49x + 86)/4(x + 2)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/4(x + 2) + (3x + 2)/(x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/4(x + 2) * (x + 10)/(x + 10) + (3x + 2)/(x + 10) * 4(x + 2)/4(x + 2)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 10)(x + 7)/4(x + 2)(x + 10) + 4(x + 2)(3x + 2)/4(x + 2)(x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 4)/2(2x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(5x^2 + 47x + 68)/2(x + 5)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(x + 5) + (x + 4)/2(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(x + 5) * 2(2x + 3)/2(2x + 3) + (x + 4)/2(2x + 3) * (x + 5)/(x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)(x + 8)/2(x + 5)(2x + 3) + (x + 5)(x + 4)/2(x + 5)(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 28x + 31)/3(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/3 + (3x + 7)/(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/3 * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (3x + 7)/(2x + 5) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)(3x + 2)/3(2x + 5) + 3(3x + 7)/3(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/4(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 4x + 11)/4(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/4 + (x + 9)/4(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/4 * 4(x + 1)/4(x + 1) + (x + 9)/4(x + 1) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)(x + 2)/16(x + 1) + 4(x + 9)/16(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 47x + 74)/2(x + 8)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 8) + (2x + 7)/2(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(x + 8) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) + (2x + 7)/2(x + 3) * (x + 8)/(x + 8)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 6(x + 3)(x + 1)/2(x + 8)(x + 3) + (x + 8)(2x + 7)/2(x + 8)(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/3,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "2(x^2 + 4x + 13)/3(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/3 - 3(x + 1)/(2x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/3 * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) - 3(x + 1)/(2x + 7) * 3/3\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)(x + 5)/3(2x + 7) - 9(x + 1)/3(2x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 4)(x)/(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) - (2x + 11)/(3x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) * (3x + 11)/(3x + 11) - (2x + 11)/(3x + 11) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)(x + 1)/(3x + 11) - (2x + 11)/(3x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x^2 + 8x + 5)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) + (4x + 9)/2(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) + (4x + 9)/2(x + 3) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)(3x + 1)/2(x + 3) + (4x + 9)/2(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(4x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "2(17x + 12)/(4x + 9)(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(4x + 9) - (x + 1)/(x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(4x + 9) * (x + 11)/(x + 11) - (x + 1)/(x + 11) * (4x + 9)/(4x + 9)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)(4x + 3)/(4x + 9)(x + 11) - (4x + 9)(x + 1)/(4x + 9)(x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(9x + 41)(x)/4(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/4 - (x + 11)/(3x + 4)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/4 * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - (x + 11)/(3x + 4) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)(3x + 11)/4(3x + 4) - 4(x + 11)/4(3x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/(x + 8)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 4)(x + 5)/(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3) - 4(x + 2)/(x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3) * (x + 8)/(x + 8) - 4(x + 2)/(x + 8) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 8)(x + 3)/(x + 8) - 4(x + 2)/(x + 8)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/4(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(5x^2 - 18x - 51)/4(x + 2)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/4(x + 2) - (x + 7)/(3x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/4(x + 2) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) - (x + 7)/(3x + 1) * 4(x + 2)/4(x + 2)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1)(3x + 5)/4(x + 2)(3x + 1) - 4(x + 2)(x + 7)/4(x + 2)(3x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 2)(12x + 31)/2(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2 + 3(x + 3)/(4x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2 * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11) + 3(x + 3)/(4x + 11) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)(3x + 4)/2(4x + 11) + 6(x + 3)/2(4x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(2x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 - 7x - 17)/(x + 2)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 2) - (x + 10)/(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 2) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) - (x + 10)/(2x + 3) * (x + 2)/(x + 2)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)(x + 1)/(x + 2)(2x + 3) - (x + 2)(x + 10)/(x + 2)(2x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2(x + 4)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 52x + 31)/2(4x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 1) + (2x + 7)/2(x + 4)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 1) * 2(x + 4)/2(x + 4) + (2x + 7)/2(x + 4) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)(2x + 3)/2(4x + 1)(x + 4) + (4x + 1)(2x + 7)/2(4x + 1)(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(x^2 + 9x + 12)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11) + (3x + 2)/(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11) * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + (3x + 2)/(x + 2) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)(2x + 11)/(x + 2) + (3x + 2)/(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(14x^2 + 22x - 33)/(x + 10)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(x + 10) - 2(x + 3)/(4x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(x + 10) * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3) - 2(x + 3)/(4x + 3) * (x + 10)/(x + 10)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)(4x + 9)/(x + 10)(4x + 3) - 2(x + 10)(x + 3)/(x + 10)(4x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/2(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 70x + 155)/2(2x + 5)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(2x + 5) + (2x + 9)/2(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(2x + 5) * 2(x + 5)/2(x + 5) + (2x + 9)/2(x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)(2x + 11)/2(2x + 5)(x + 5) + (2x + 5)(2x + 9)/2(2x + 5)(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(4x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/(2x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(14x^2 + 35x + 15)/(4x + 3)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(4x + 3) - 4(x + 2)/(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(4x + 3) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) - 4(x + 2)/(2x + 3) * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)(x + 3)/(4x + 3)(2x + 3) - 4(4x + 3)(x + 2)/(4x + 3)(2x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/3(x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 - 7x - 14)/12(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/4 - (4x + 5)/3(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/4 * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) - (4x + 5)/3(x + 1) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)(x + 2)/12(x + 1) - 4(4x + 5)/12(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d 2\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(5x + 2)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 2) - 2\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 2) * 1/1 - 2 * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 2) - 2(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "5(2x^2 + 8x + 5)/(2x + 7)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(2x + 7) + (3x + 2)/(4x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(2x + 7) * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11) + (3x + 2)/(4x + 11) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)(x + 1)/(2x + 7)(4x + 11) + (2x + 7)(3x + 2)/(2x + 7)(4x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 14x + 13)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7) + 3(x + 2)/(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7) * (x + 1)/(x + 1) + 3(x + 2)/(x + 1) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)(4x + 7)/(x + 1) + 3(x + 2)/(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 8x + 7)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 - (4x + 7)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 * (x + 3)/(x + 3) - (4x + 7)/(x + 3) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)(3x + 7)/2(x + 3) - 2(4x + 7)/2(x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 17x + 27)/2(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2 - (2x + 11)/(x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2 * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - (2x + 11)/(x + 7) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)(2x + 7)/2(x + 7) - 2(2x + 11)/2(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 4)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 15x + 38)/2(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2 + (x + 1)/(x + 4)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2 * (x + 4)/(x + 4) + (x + 1)/(x + 4) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)(x + 9)/2(x + 4) + 2(x + 1)/2(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 18x + 23)/3(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/3 + (3x + 7)/(3x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/3 * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) + (3x + 7)/(3x + 1) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1)(3x + 2)/3(3x + 1) + 3(3x + 7)/3(3x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 45x + 62)/2(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2 + (4x + 9)/(x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2 * (x + 11)/(x + 11) + (4x + 9)/(x + 11) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)(3x + 4)/2(x + 11) + 2(4x + 9)/2(x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 35x + 35)/4(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/4 - (2x + 7)/(x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/4 * (x + 9)/(x + 9) - (2x + 7)/(x + 9) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)(4x + 7)/4(x + 9) - 4(2x + 7)/4(x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(3x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 14x + 34)/(2x + 7)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(2x + 7) - (4x + 3)/(3x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(2x + 7) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) - (4x + 3)/(3x + 5) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)(3x + 11)/(2x + 7)(3x + 5) - (2x + 7)(4x + 3)/(2x + 7)(3x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/2(2x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 9x + 12)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2 + (2x + 9)/2(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2 * 2(2x + 5)/2(2x + 5) + (2x + 9)/2(2x + 5) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 5)(2x + 3)/4(2x + 5) + 2(2x + 9)/4(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(4x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(8x^2 + 20x + 17)/(4x + 11)(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(4x + 11) + (2x + 3)/(4x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(4x + 11) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1) + (2x + 3)/(4x + 1) * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)(2x + 1)/(4x + 11)(4x + 1) + (4x + 11)(2x + 3)/(4x + 11)(4x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 10x + 17)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7) + (x + 10)/(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7) * (x + 1)/(x + 1) + (x + 10)/(x + 1) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)(2x + 7)/(x + 1) + (x + 10)/(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(16x^2 + 38x + 19)/2(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2 + 3(x + 2)/(4x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2 * (4x + 7)/(4x + 7) + 3(x + 2)/(4x + 7) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)(4x + 1)/2(4x + 7) + 6(x + 2)/2(4x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 43x + 74)/(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3) + (3x + 8)/(3x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3) * (3x + 11)/(3x + 11) + (3x + 8)/(3x + 11) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(3x + 11)(x + 3)/(3x + 11) + (3x + 8)/(3x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(7x^2 + 35x + 38)/(x + 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 5) + (3x + 7)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 5) * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + (3x + 7)/(x + 3) * (x + 5)/(x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)(4x + 1)/(x + 5)(x + 3) + (x + 5)(3x + 7)/(x + 5)(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 4)(4x + 13)/(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) - (2x + 3)/(4x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11) - (2x + 3)/(4x + 11) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)(x + 5)/(4x + 11) - (2x + 3)/(4x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2(2x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(5x^2 + 67x + 136)/2(x + 10)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x + 10) + (x + 7)/2(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x + 10) * 2(2x + 3)/2(2x + 3) + (x + 7)/2(2x + 3) * (x + 10)/(x + 10)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)(x + 11)/2(x + 10)(2x + 3) + (x + 10)(x + 7)/2(x + 10)(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/3(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(11x^2 + 46x + 51)/3(2x + 7)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x + 7) + (x + 3)/3(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x + 7) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2) + (x + 3)/3(x + 2) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)(3x + 5)/3(2x + 7)(x + 2) + (2x + 7)(x + 3)/3(2x + 7)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 4)/3,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/(4x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 26x + 31)/3(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/3 + 3(x + 3)/(4x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/3 * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1) + 3(x + 3)/(4x + 1) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)(x + 4)/3(4x + 1) + 9(x + 3)/3(4x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/2,\ng(x) \u003d 1/3\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(6x + 1)/6", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/2 - 1/3\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/2 * 3/3 - 1/3 * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(2x + 1)/6 - 2/6\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2(2x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(11x^2 + 41x + 20)/6(x + 2)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3(x + 2) + (x + 1)/2(2x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3(x + 2) * 2(2x + 1)/2(2x + 1) + (x + 1)/2(2x + 1) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)(2x + 7)/6(x + 2)(2x + 1) + 3(x + 2)(x + 1)/6(x + 2)(2x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3(x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 29x + 42)/12(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/4 - (4x + 3)/3(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/4 * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2) - (4x + 3)/3(x + 2) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 9(x + 2)(x + 3)/12(x + 2) - 4(4x + 3)/12(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(x + 9)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x + 7)/(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 9) + (4x + 5)/(x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 9) * (x + 9)/(x + 9) + (4x + 5)/(x + 9) * (x + 9)/(x + 9)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)(2x + 9)/(x + 9)(x + 9) + (x + 9)(4x + 5)/(x + 9)(x + 9)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 3x + 3)/(3x + 11)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 11) - (x + 2)/(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 11) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) - (x + 2)/(2x + 5) * (3x + 11)/(3x + 11)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)(2x + 5)/(3x + 11)(2x + 5) - (3x + 11)(x + 2)/(3x + 11)(2x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x^2 + 10x + 5)/(4x + 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(4x + 1) + (x + 5)/(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(4x + 1) * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + (x + 5)/(x + 2) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)(2x + 5)/(4x + 1)(x + 2) + (4x + 1)(x + 5)/(4x + 1)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(10x^2 + 52x + 65)/2(x + 2)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2(x + 2) + (x + 5)/(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2(x + 2) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (x + 5)/(2x + 5) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)(4x + 9)/2(x + 2)(2x + 5) + 2(x + 2)(x + 5)/2(x + 2)(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 19x + 27)/2(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2 - (2x + 9)/(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2 * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) - (2x + 9)/(2x + 5) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)(x + 9)/2(2x + 5) - 2(2x + 9)/2(2x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 6)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 39x + 21)/3(x + 6)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3 + (4x + 1)/(x + 6)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3 * (x + 6)/(x + 6) + (4x + 1)/(x + 6) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 6)(4x + 3)/3(x + 6) + 3(4x + 1)/3(x + 6)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 3x + 8)/2(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/2 - (2x + 1)/(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/2 * (x + 2)/(x + 2) - (2x + 1)/(x + 2) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)(x + 5)/2(x + 2) - 2(2x + 1)/2(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 18x + 11)/3(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)/3 - (4x + 11)/(2x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)/3 * (2x + 11)/(2x + 11) - (4x + 11)/(2x + 11) * 3/3\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 11)(x + 2)/3(2x + 11) - 3(4x + 11)/3(2x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(3x + 10)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 32x + 40)/4(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/4 - (4x + 5)/(3x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/4 * (3x + 10)/(3x + 10) - (4x + 5)/(3x + 10) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(3x + 10)(x + 2)/4(3x + 10) - 4(4x + 5)/4(3x + 10)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)/3,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/2(x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 19x + 31)/6(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)/3 - 3(x + 1)/2(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)/3 * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) - 3(x + 1)/2(x + 2) * 3/3\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)(x + 5)/6(x + 2) - 9(x + 1)/6(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(5x + 8)/(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 5) + 4(x + 1)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 5) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) + 4(x + 1)/(x + 5) * (x + 5)/(x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(x + 4)/(x + 5)(x + 5) + 4(x + 5)(x + 1)/(x + 5)(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 30x + 65)/(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4) - (4x + 7)/(2x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4) * (2x + 9)/(2x + 9) - (4x + 7)/(2x + 9) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 9)(x + 4)/(2x + 9) - (4x + 7)/(2x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(3x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(3x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 12x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(3x + 4) - (2x + 1)/(3x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) - (2x + 1)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)(4x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 5) - (3x + 4)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 4)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 31x + 47)/3(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/3 + (4x + 1)/(x + 4)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/3 * (x + 4)/(x + 4) + (4x + 1)/(x + 4) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)(2x + 11)/3(x + 4) + 3(4x + 1)/3(x + 4)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/2(2x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 1)/(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(10x^2 + 35x + 37)/2(2x + 3)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/2(2x + 3) + 2(x + 1)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/2(2x + 3) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) + 2(x + 1)/(x + 5) * 2(2x + 3)/2(2x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(2x + 5)/2(2x + 3)(x + 5) + 4(2x + 3)(x + 1)/2(2x + 3)(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(4x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/3(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 2)(15x + 19)/3(4x + 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(4x + 5) + (3x + 7)/3(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(4x + 5) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) + (3x + 7)/3(x + 1) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)(x + 1)/3(4x + 5)(x + 1) + (4x + 5)(3x + 7)/3(4x + 5)(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/3(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 3\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(5x + 9)/3(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/3(x + 1) + 3\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/3(x + 1) * 1/1 + 3 * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/3(x + 1) + 9(x + 1)/3(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/2(x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 15x + 47)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2 - (x + 8)/2(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2 * 2(x + 5)/2(x + 5) - (x + 8)/2(x + 5) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)(x + 11)/4(x + 5) - 2(x + 8)/4(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x^2 + 23x + 33)/(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7) - (x + 11)/(2x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7) * (2x + 11)/(2x + 11) - (x + 11)/(2x + 11) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)(3x + 7)/(2x + 11) - (x + 11)/(2x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/3(x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 7x - 7)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2 - (4x + 5)/3(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2 * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) - (4x + 5)/3(x + 1) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)(4x + 1)/6(x + 1) - 2(4x + 5)/6(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 19x + 15)/2(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2 + (4x + 3)/(2x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2 * (2x + 9)/(2x + 9) + (4x + 3)/(2x + 9) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)(x + 1)/2(2x + 9) + 2(4x + 3)/2(2x + 9)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 12x + 13)/(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) + (x + 4)/(2x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) * (2x + 9)/(2x + 9) + (x + 4)/(2x + 9) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)(x + 1)/(2x + 9) + (x + 4)/(2x + 9)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 37x + 58)/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7) + (2x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (2x + 9)/(3x + 7) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)(2x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (2x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(3x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 49x + 54)/4(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/4 + (x + 1)/(3x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/4 * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + (x + 1)/(3x + 5) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)(3x + 10)/4(3x + 5) + 4(x + 1)/4(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 4)(7x + 10)/(x + 1)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 1) + (3x + 7)/(2x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 1) * (2x + 11)/(2x + 11) + (3x + 7)/(2x + 11) * (x + 1)/(x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)(2x + 3)/(x + 1)(2x + 11) + (x + 1)(3x + 7)/(x + 1)(2x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(x + 8)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "3(x^2 + 15x + 57)/(x + 11)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 11) + (x + 9)/(x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 11) * (x + 8)/(x + 8) + (x + 9)/(x + 8) * (x + 11)/(x + 11)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 8)(2x + 9)/(x + 11)(x + 8) + (x + 11)(x + 9)/(x + 11)(x + 8)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 2)(9x + 44)/(x + 11)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(x + 11) + (x + 1)/(2x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(x + 11) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) + (x + 1)/(2x + 7) * (x + 11)/(x + 11)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)(4x + 11)/(x + 11)(2x + 7) + (x + 11)(x + 1)/(x + 11)(2x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(16x^2 + 34x + 1)/2(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/2 - (3x + 10)/(4x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/2 * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3) - (3x + 10)/(4x + 3) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)(4x + 7)/2(4x + 3) - 2(3x + 10)/2(4x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(2x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(3x + 8)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(7x^2 + 30x + 38)/(2x + 3)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(2x + 3) + 4(x + 1)/(3x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(2x + 3) * (3x + 8)/(3x + 8) + 4(x + 1)/(3x + 8) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(3x + 8)(x + 4)/(2x + 3)(3x + 8) + 4(2x + 3)(x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 8)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(4x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 2x + 1)/(4x + 7)(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(4x + 7) - (2x + 1)/(3x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(4x + 7) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) - (2x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (4x + 7)/(4x + 7)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 4(3x + 2)(x + 1)/(4x + 7)(3x + 2) - (4x + 7)(2x + 1)/(4x + 7)(3x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 6)/2(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(4x^2 + 21x + 46)/2(x + 4)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 6)/2(x + 4) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 6)/2(x + 4) * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 3) * 2(x + 4)/2(x + 4)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)(x + 6)/2(x + 4)(4x + 3) - 8(x + 4)(x + 2)/2(x + 4)(4x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/2(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(x + 9)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 55x + 127)/2(x + 2)(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/2(x + 2) + (3x + 7)/(x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/2(x + 2) * (x + 9)/(x + 9) + (3x + 7)/(x + 9) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)(2x + 11)/2(x + 2)(x + 9) + 2(x + 2)(3x + 7)/2(x + 2)(x + 9)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/2(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x + 8)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "5(x + 2)(3x + 10)/2(2x + 1)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/2(2x + 1) + (3x + 10)/(x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/2(2x + 1) * (x + 8)/(x + 8) + (3x + 10)/(x + 8) * 2(2x + 1)/2(2x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 8)(3x + 10)/2(2x + 1)(x + 8) + 2(2x + 1)(3x + 10)/2(2x + 1)(x + 8)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/3(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 2)(12x + 41)/3(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9) + (2x + 1)/3(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9) * 3(x + 3)/3(x + 3) + (2x + 1)/3(x + 3) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)(4x + 9)/3(x + 3) + (2x + 1)/3(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 25x + 85)/2(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2 + (x + 11)/(2x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2 * (2x + 9)/(2x + 9) + (x + 11)/(2x + 9) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 9)(x + 7)/2(2x + 9) + 2(x + 11)/2(2x + 9)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 55x + 112)/2(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2 + (3x + 11)/(x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/2 * (x + 10)/(x + 10) + (3x + 11)/(x + 10) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 10)(4x + 9)/2(x + 10) + 2(3x + 11)/2(x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/2(x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 27x + 8)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3) - (3x + 10)/2(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) - (3x + 10)/2(x + 3) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)(4x + 3)/2(x + 3) - (3x + 10)/2(x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/3(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 5)/(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(8x^2 + 29x + 23)/3(x + 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/3(x + 1) + 2(2x + 5)/(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/3(x + 1) * (x + 2)/(x + 2) + 2(2x + 5)/(x + 2) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)(x + 2)/3(x + 1)(x + 2) + 6(x + 1)(2x + 5)/3(x + 1)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)/(3x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(2x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(17x^2 + 52x + 17)/(3x + 1)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)/(3x + 1) + (3x + 11)/(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)/(3x + 1) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) + (3x + 11)/(2x + 3) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)(2x + 3) + (3x + 1)(3x + 11)/(3x + 1)(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(2x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(3x^2 + 10x + 11)/(2x + 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(2x + 3) - 2(x + 3)/(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(2x + 3) * (x + 1)/(x + 1) - 2(x + 3)/(x + 1) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)(x + 7)/(2x + 3)(x + 1) - 2(2x + 3)(x + 3)/(2x + 3)(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 8)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(5x^2 + 33x + 50)/(x + 10)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x + 10) + (x + 2)/(3x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x + 10) * (3x + 8)/(3x + 8) + (x + 2)/(3x + 8) * (x + 10)/(x + 10)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8)(3x + 10)/(x + 10)(3x + 8) + (x + 10)(x + 2)/(x + 10)(3x + 8)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 5x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1) + (x + 4)/(2x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1) + (x + 4)/(2x + 1) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1) + (x + 4)/(2x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/2(x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 2x + 4)/2(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/2 - (4x + 1)/2(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/2 * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) - (4x + 1)/2(x + 1) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 1)(x + 5)/4(x + 1) - 2(4x + 1)/4(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/3(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 18x + 21)/3(x + 3)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 3) + (x + 3)/3(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 3) * 3(x + 2)/3(x + 2) + (x + 3)/3(x + 2) * (x + 3)/(x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)(x + 2)/3(x + 3)(x + 2) + (x + 3)(x + 3)/3(x + 3)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "12/(x + 8)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 8) - (x + 1)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(x + 8) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) - (x + 1)/(x + 5) * (x + 8)/(x + 8)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(x + 4)/(x + 8)(x + 5) - (x + 8)(x + 1)/(x + 8)(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 23x + 19)/4(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/4 + (3x + 4)/(3x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/4 * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) + (3x + 4)/(3x + 1) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1)(2x + 3)/4(3x + 1) + 4(3x + 4)/4(3x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(4x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/3(x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(9x^2 + 31x + 43)/3(4x + 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(4x + 7) - (3x + 10)/3(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(4x + 7) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) - (3x + 10)/3(x + 1) * (4x + 7)/(4x + 7)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)(x + 9)/3(4x + 7)(x + 1) - (4x + 7)(3x + 10)/3(4x + 7)(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x^2 + 11x + 7)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) + (x + 11)/2(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) * 2(x + 5)/2(x + 5) + (x + 11)/2(x + 5) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)(3x + 1)/2(x + 5) + (x + 11)/2(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 5)/(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 14x + 35)/(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) + 2(2x + 5)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) + 2(2x + 5)/(x + 5) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(x + 5)/(x + 5) + 2(2x + 5)/(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 5x + 14)/(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 4) - 2(2x + 3)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 4) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) - 2(2x + 3)/(x + 5) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(x + 4)/(x + 5) - 2(2x + 3)/(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x^2 + 17x + 23)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3) + (x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5) + (x + 1)/(2x + 5) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(2x + 5)(x + 3)/(2x + 5) + (x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(4x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 9x + 7)/(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2) - (4x + 3)/(4x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5) - (4x + 3)/(4x + 5) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5)(x + 2)/(4x + 5) - (4x + 3)/(4x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 20x + 34)/(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8) + (3x + 10)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8) * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + (3x + 10)/(x + 3) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)(3x + 8)/(x + 3) + (3x + 10)/(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 31x + 10)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1) + (x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) + (x + 3)/(2x + 7) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)(4x + 1)/(2x + 7) + (x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/4(x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 23x + 14)/4(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) - (x + 6)/4(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5) * 4(x + 1)/4(x + 1) - (x + 6)/4(x + 1) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)(x + 5)/4(x + 1) - (x + 6)/4(x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 7)(3x + 19)/4(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/4 + (x + 3)/(2x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/4 * (2x + 11)/(2x + 11) + (x + 3)/(2x + 11) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)(3x + 11)/4(2x + 11) + 4(x + 3)/4(2x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 58x + 61)/2(x + 3)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2(x + 3) + 3(x + 3)/(3x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2(x + 3) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1) + 3(x + 3)/(3x + 1) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1)(x + 7)/2(x + 3)(3x + 1) + 6(x + 3)(x + 3)/2(x + 3)(3x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/2,\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 19x + 8)/2(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/2 - 2(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/2 * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4) - 2(2x + 3)/(3x + 4) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)(3x + 5)/2(3x + 4) - 4(2x + 3)/2(3x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 59x + 73)/3(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/3 + (4x + 1)/(x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/3 * (x + 10)/(x + 10) + (4x + 1)/(x + 10) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 10)(4x + 7)/3(x + 10) + 3(4x + 1)/3(x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(14x^2 - 10x - 27)/(4x + 1)(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(4x + 1) - (4x + 1)/(x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)/(4x + 1) * (x + 7)/(x + 7) - (4x + 1)/(x + 7) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 7)(x + 2)/(4x + 1)(x + 7) - (4x + 1)(4x + 1)/(4x + 1)(x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 25x + 1)/2(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2 - (3x + 10)/(4x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/2 * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3) - (3x + 10)/(4x + 3) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)(x + 7)/2(4x + 3) - 2(3x + 10)/2(4x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/4,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 1)/(4x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 14x + 1)/4(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/4 - 2(x + 1)/(4x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/4 * (4x + 9)/(4x + 9) - 2(x + 1)/(4x + 9) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)(2x + 1)/4(4x + 9) - 8(x + 1)/4(4x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 5)(4x + 7)/4(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/4 - (3x + 7)/(2x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/4 * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) - (3x + 7)/(2x + 7) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)(4x + 9)/4(2x + 7) - 4(3x + 7)/4(2x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/2(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(15x^2 + 94x + 135)/2(x + 5)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/2(x + 5) + (3x + 8)/(3x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/2(x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 5) + (3x + 8)/(3x + 5) * 2(x + 5)/2(x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 5)(3x + 11)/2(x + 5)(3x + 5) + 2(x + 5)(3x + 8)/2(x + 5)(3x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 13)/4(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/4 - (3x + 2)/(3x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/4 * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) - (3x + 2)/(3x + 7) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)(2x + 3)/4(3x + 7) - 4(3x + 2)/4(3x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 14x + 17)/(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) + (x + 7)/(3x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1) * (3x + 10)/(3x + 10) + (x + 7)/(3x + 10) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)(x + 1)/(3x + 10) + (x + 7)/(3x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(3x + 8)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(10x^2 - 5x - 58)/(4x + 5)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 5) - 2(2x + 3)/(3x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 5) * (3x + 8)/(3x + 8) - 2(2x + 3)/(3x + 8) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8)(2x + 11)/(4x + 5)(3x + 8) - 2(4x + 5)(2x + 3)/(4x + 5)(3x + 8)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 2)(6x + 17)/3(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3 - (x + 3)/(3x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3 * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) - (x + 3)/(3x + 7) * 3/3\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)(4x + 11)/3(3x + 7) - 3(x + 3)/3(3x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/4,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x - 26)/4(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/4 - 2(x + 5)/(3x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/4 * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) - 2(x + 5)/(3x + 2) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)(2x + 7)/4(3x + 2) - 8(x + 5)/4(3x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 25x + 83)/2(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2 - 2(x + 4)/(2x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)/2 * (2x + 11)/(2x + 11) - 2(x + 4)/(2x + 11) * 2/2\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)(x + 9)/2(2x + 11) - 4(x + 4)/2(2x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(3x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(9x^2 + 28x + 9)/(3x + 7)(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(3x + 7) + (4x + 1)/(3x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(3x + 7) * (3x + 11)/(3x + 11) + (4x + 1)/(3x + 11) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)(2x + 1)/(3x + 7)(3x + 11) + (3x + 7)(4x + 1)/(3x + 7)(3x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 45x + 79)/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5) + (x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (x + 9)/(3x + 7) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(3x + 7)(x + 5)/(3x + 7) + (x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 27x + 57)/4(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/4 + (2x + 9)/(4x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/4 * (4x + 7)/(4x + 7) + (2x + 9)/(4x + 7) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)(x + 3)/4(4x + 7) + 4(2x + 9)/4(4x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/2(2x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(25x^2 + 72x + 45)/6(x + 1)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3(x + 1) + 3(x + 3)/2(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/3(x + 1) * 2(2x + 3)/2(2x + 3) + 3(x + 3)/2(2x + 3) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)(4x + 3)/6(x + 1)(2x + 3) + 9(x + 1)(x + 3)/6(x + 1)(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/2(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 27x + 42)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3) + 3(x + 2)/2(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3) + 3(x + 2)/2(x + 3) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 3)(x + 3)/2(x + 3) + 3(x + 2)/2(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(x + 8)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(5x^2 + 28x + 34)/(x + 3)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 3) + 2(2x + 3)/(x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 3) * (x + 8)/(x + 8) + 2(2x + 3)/(x + 8) * (x + 3)/(x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 8)(x + 2)/(x + 3)(x + 8) + 2(x + 3)(2x + 3)/(x + 3)(x + 8)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 8)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(23x + 67)/(2x + 7)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x + 7) - (2x + 3)/(x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x + 7) * (x + 8)/(x + 8) - (2x + 3)/(x + 8) * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 8)(4x + 11)/(2x + 7)(x + 8) - (2x + 7)(2x + 3)/(2x + 7)(x + 8)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 16x + 51)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2 + (x + 9)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2 * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + (x + 9)/(x + 3) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)(x + 11)/2(x + 3) + 2(x + 9)/2(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(10x^2 + 25x + 57)/(3x + 2)(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x + 2) + (3x + 1)/(x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x + 2) * (x + 11)/(x + 11) + (3x + 1)/(x + 11) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)(x + 5)/(3x + 2)(x + 11) + (3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 2)(x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "10(-3x - 7)/(x + 9)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 9) - (4x + 9)/(4x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 9) * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11) - (4x + 9)/(4x + 11) * (x + 9)/(x + 9)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)(x + 1)/(x + 9)(4x + 11) - (x + 9)(4x + 9)/(x + 9)(4x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/2(x + 4)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(8x^2 + 19x - 25)/2(4x + 7)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 7) - 3(x + 3)/2(x + 4)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 7) * 2(x + 4)/2(x + 4) - 3(x + 3)/2(x + 4) * (4x + 7)/(4x + 7)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)(2x + 11)/2(4x + 7)(x + 4) - 3(4x + 7)(x + 3)/2(4x + 7)(x + 4)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 16x + 17)/2(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2 + (3x + 5)/(3x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2 * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) + (3x + 5)/(3x + 7) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)(x + 1)/2(3x + 7) + 2(3x + 5)/2(3x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/2(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 28x + 37)/6(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3 + (2x + 3)/2(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3 * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) + (2x + 3)/2(x + 2) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)(2x + 7)/6(x + 2) + 3(2x + 3)/6(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "3(4x^2 + 21x + 29)/2(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 + (x + 5)/(4x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11) + (x + 5)/(4x + 11) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)(3x + 7)/2(4x + 11) + 2(x + 5)/2(4x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)(11x + 27)/(3x + 8)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 8) + (x + 6)/(4x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 8) * (4x + 11)/(4x + 11) + (x + 6)/(4x + 11) * (3x + 8)/(3x + 8)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)(2x + 3)/(3x + 8)(4x + 11) + (3x + 8)(x + 6)/(3x + 8)(4x + 11)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/2(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(7x^2 + 59x + 106)/2(x + 1)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/2(x + 1) + 2(x + 4)/(x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/2(x + 1) * (x + 10)/(x + 10) + 2(x + 4)/(x + 10) * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 10)(x + 3)/2(x + 1)(x + 10) + 4(x + 1)(x + 4)/2(x + 1)(x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/2(x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(6x^2 - 15x - 29)/2(3x + 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x + 1) - (4x + 3)/2(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x + 1) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) - (4x + 3)/2(x + 2) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)(3x + 8)/2(3x + 1)(x + 2) - (3x + 1)(4x + 3)/2(3x + 1)(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/2(2x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(15x^2 + 84x + 113)/2(x + 3)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x + 3) + (3x + 1)/2(2x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x + 3) * 2(2x + 5)/2(2x + 5) + (3x + 1)/2(2x + 5) * (x + 3)/(x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 5)(3x + 11)/2(x + 3)(2x + 5) + (x + 3)(3x + 1)/2(x + 3)(2x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/2(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 21x + 44)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3 + (x + 10)/2(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/3 * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1) + (x + 10)/2(x + 1) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 1)(2x + 7)/6(x + 1) + 3(x + 10)/6(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(17x^2 + 86x + 83)/(2x + 9)(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x + 9) + (4x + 7)/(3x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x + 9) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) + (4x + 7)/(3x + 2) * (2x + 9)/(2x + 9)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)(3x + 10)/(2x + 9)(3x + 2) + (2x + 9)(4x + 7)/(2x + 9)(3x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 16x + 23)/2(x + 3)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2(x + 3) + (2x + 7)/2(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2(x + 3) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) + (2x + 7)/2(x + 2) * 2(x + 3)/2(x + 3)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)(x + 1)/4(x + 3)(x + 2) + 2(x + 3)(2x + 7)/4(x + 3)(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/4,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)/(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 21x + 49)/4(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/4 + 2(x + 5)/(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/4 * (x + 1)/(x + 1) + 2(x + 5)/(x + 1) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)(4x + 9)/4(x + 1) + 8(x + 5)/4(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(4x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(16x^2 + 23x - 6)/(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5) - (x + 11)/(4x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1) - (x + 11)/(4x + 1) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)(4x + 5)/(4x + 1) - (x + 11)/(4x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(4x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(2x + 3)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-2(2x^2 + 4x - 3)/(4x + 3)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(4x + 3) - 2(x + 3)/(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(4x + 3) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) - 2(x + 3)/(2x + 3) * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)(x + 4)/(4x + 3)(2x + 3) - 2(4x + 3)(x + 3)/(4x + 3)(2x + 3)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 34x + 25)/(x + 4)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 4) + (2x + 5)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 4) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) + (2x + 5)/(x + 5) * (x + 4)/(x + 4)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(4x + 1)/(x + 4)(x + 5) + (x + 4)(2x + 5)/(x + 4)(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/4,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 1)/(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 15x + 11)/4(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/4 + 2(x + 1)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/4 * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + 2(x + 1)/(x + 3) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)(2x + 1)/4(x + 3) + 8(x + 1)/4(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/4,\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 47x + 26)/4(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/4 + 4(x + 1)/(x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/4 * (x + 10)/(x + 10) + 4(x + 1)/(x + 10) * 4/4\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 10)(3x + 1)/4(x + 10) + 16(x + 1)/4(x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 10)/2(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 11)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 14)(-x + 7)/2(x + 2)(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 10)/2(x + 2) - (2x + 3)/(x + 11)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 10)/2(x + 2) * (x + 11)/(x + 11) - (2x + 3)/(x + 11) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)(x + 10)/2(x + 2)(x + 11) - 2(x + 2)(2x + 3)/2(x + 2)(x + 11)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(x + 5)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(13x^2 + 67x + 70)/(3x + 11)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 11) + (4x + 5)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 11) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) + (4x + 5)/(x + 5) * (3x + 11)/(3x + 11)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(x + 3)/(3x + 11)(x + 5) + (3x + 11)(4x + 5)/(3x + 11)(x + 5)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/2(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/(x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(4x^2 - 13x - 21)/2(x + 2)(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/2(x + 2) - 2(2x + 3)/(x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/2(x + 2) * (x + 9)/(x + 9) - 2(2x + 3)/(x + 9) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 9)(4x + 5)/2(x + 2)(x + 9) - 4(x + 2)(2x + 3)/2(x + 2)(x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 10)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 46x + 50)/2(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2 + (2x + 5)/(3x + 10)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/2 * (3x + 10)/(3x + 10) + (2x + 5)/(3x + 10) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 10)(3x + 4)/2(3x + 10) + 2(2x + 5)/2(3x + 10)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(4x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 10x + 7)/(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2) - 3(x + 1)/(4x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 2) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5) - 3(x + 1)/(4x + 5) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5)(x + 2)/(4x + 5) - 3(x + 1)/(4x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/4,\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/4(x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 10x + 13)/4(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/4 - (3x + 1)/4(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/4 * 4(x + 2)/4(x + 2) - (3x + 1)/4(x + 2) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)(3x + 7)/16(x + 2) - 4(3x + 1)/16(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(4x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(4x^2 + 16x + 19)/(4x + 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(4x + 5) + (x + 1)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(4x + 5) * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + (x + 1)/(x + 3) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)(4x + 11)/(4x + 5)(x + 3) + (4x + 5)(x + 1)/(4x + 5)(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/2(x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 14x + 29)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3) - (2x + 1)/2(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3) * 2(x + 5)/2(x + 5) - (2x + 1)/2(x + 5) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 5)(x + 3)/2(x + 5) - (2x + 1)/2(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/3,\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 4)/(4x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)(12x + 13)/3(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/3 - 2(x + 4)/(4x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/3 * (4x + 9)/(4x + 9) - 2(x + 4)/(4x + 9) * 3/3\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)(3x + 7)/3(4x + 9) - 6(x + 4)/3(4x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 1/2,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 2)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x + 14)/2(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 1/2 + 3(x + 2)/(3x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 1/2 * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) + 3(x + 2)/(3x + 2) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/2(3x + 2) + 6(x + 2)/2(3x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/4(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 77x + 39)/4(4x + 1)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(4x + 1) + (x + 11)/4(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(4x + 1) * 4(x + 1)/4(x + 1) + (x + 11)/4(x + 1) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)(x + 7)/4(4x + 1)(x + 1) + (4x + 1)(x + 11)/4(4x + 1)(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 29x + 26)/2(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 + (x + 6)/(3x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/2 * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2) + (x + 6)/(3x + 2) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 2)(3x + 7)/2(3x + 2) + 2(x + 6)/2(3x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 8)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 50x + 51)/3(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/3 + (4x + 1)/(x + 8)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/3 * (x + 8)/(x + 8) + (4x + 1)/(x + 8) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 8)(2x + 3)/3(x + 8) + 3(4x + 1)/3(x + 8)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 4)/3,\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 6x + 1)/3(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/3 - 3(x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 4)/3 * (2x + 7)/(2x + 7) - 3(x + 3)/(2x + 7) * 3/3\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)(x + 4)/3(2x + 7) - 9(x + 3)/3(2x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/2(x + 2)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 21x + 6)/2(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3) - (x + 6)/2(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3) * 2(x + 2)/2(x + 2) - (x + 6)/2(x + 2) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 2)(4x + 3)/2(x + 2) - (x + 6)/2(x + 2)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(2x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 54x + 29)/2(x + 4)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2(x + 4) + (4x + 1)/(2x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/2(x + 4) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3) + (4x + 1)/(2x + 3) * 2(x + 4)/2(x + 4)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 3)(2x + 7)/2(x + 4)(2x + 3) + 2(x + 4)(4x + 1)/2(x + 4)(2x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/3,\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 21x + 21)/3(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/3 + (x + 1)/(x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 3)/3 * (x + 3)/(x + 3) + (x + 1)/(x + 3) * 3/3\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)(2x + 3)/3(x + 3) + 3(x + 1)/3(x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/2(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d 2(2x + 5)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(28x^2 + 121x + 124)/2(2x + 5)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/2(2x + 5) + 2(2x + 5)/(4x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/2(2x + 5) * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3) + 2(2x + 5)/(4x + 3) * 2(2x + 5)/2(2x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 3)(3x + 8)/2(2x + 5)(4x + 3) + 4(2x + 5)(2x + 5)/2(2x + 5)(4x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 3)(x + 4)/(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5) - (x + 1)/(x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (2x + 5) * (x + 5)/(x + 5) - (x + 1)/(x + 5) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 5)(2x + 5)/(x + 5) - (x + 1)/(x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 14x + 21)/(x + 2)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(x + 2) - (2x + 3)/(4x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(x + 2) * (4x + 9)/(4x + 9) - (2x + 3)/(4x + 9) * (x + 2)/(x + 2)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 9)(x + 3)/(x + 2)(4x + 9) - (x + 2)(2x + 3)/(x + 2)(4x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 2(x + 3)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "2(12x^2 + 23x + 6)/(4x + 1)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)/(4x + 1) + 2(x + 3)/(4x + 3)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(2x + 1)/(4x + 1) * (4x + 3)/(4x + 3) + 2(x + 3)/(4x + 3) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 2(4x + 3)(2x + 1)/(4x + 1)(4x + 3) + 2(4x + 1)(x + 3)/(4x + 1)(4x + 3)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(3x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/(4x + 5)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "-(8x^2 + 23x + 26)/(3x + 7)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(3x + 7) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 5)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(3x + 7) * (4x + 5)/(4x + 5) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 5) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 5)(x + 6)/(3x + 7)(4x + 5) - 4(3x + 7)(x + 2)/(3x + 7)(4x + 5)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)/(4x + 1)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(12x^2 + 3x - 7)/(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 1) * (4x + 1)/(4x + 1) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 1) * 1/1\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (4x + 1)(3x + 1)/(4x + 1) - 4(x + 2)/(4x + 1)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3)/2(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)(-x + 3)/2(x + 1)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/2(x + 1) - 3(x + 1)/(3x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (x + 3)/2(x + 1) * (3x + 7)/(3x + 7) - 3(x + 1)/(3x + 7) * 2(x + 1)/2(x + 1)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d (3x + 7)(x + 3)/2(x + 1)(3x + 7) - 6(x + 1)(x + 1)/2(x + 1)(3x + 7)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2,\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/4(x + 2)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(2x^2 + 8x + 11)/4(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2 + (2x + 7)/4(x + 2)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 1)/2 * 4(x + 2)/4(x + 2) + (2x + 7)/4(x + 2) * 2/2\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 4(x + 2)(x + 1)/8(x + 2) + 2(2x + 7)/8(x + 2)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/3(x + 1)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(19x^2 + 120x + 143)/6(2x + 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2(2x + 5) + (4x + 11)/3(x + 1)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (x + 11)/2(2x + 5) * 3(x + 1)/3(x + 1) + (4x + 11)/3(x + 1) * 2(2x + 5)/2(2x + 5)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 1)(x + 11)/6(2x + 5)(x + 1) + 2(2x + 5)(4x + 11)/6(2x + 5)(x + 1)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/4,\ng(x) \u003d 4(x + 1)/(x + 9)\nFind (f - g)(x)", "answer": "(3x^2 + 20x + 65)/4(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function subtraction property, (f - g)(x) \u003d f(x) - g(x)\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/4 - 4(x + 1)/(x + 9)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 3)/4 * (x + 9)/(x + 9) - 4(x + 1)/(x + 9) * 4/4\n(f - g)(x) \u003d 3(x + 9)(x + 3)/4(x + 9) - 16(x + 1)/4(x + 9)\nSubtract the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f - g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f + g)(x)", "answer": "(8x^2 + 43x + 52)/(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function addition property, (f + g)(x) \u003d f(x) + g(x)\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7) + (x + 3)/(4x + 7)\nEqualize the denominators\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (2x + 7) * (4x + 7)/(4x + 7) + (x + 3)/(4x + 7) * 1/1\n(f + g)(x) \u003d (4x + 7)(2x + 7)/(4x + 7) + (x + 3)/(4x + 7)\nAdd the two expressions, then simplify", "prompt": "(f + g)(x) \u003d"}
]}